Guide to the Connecticut AIDS Action Council 1990-2002 GLBTQ.2011.01 GLBTQ.2011.01
GLBTQ Archives, Central Connecticut State University
- Administrative Records
  - Insurance and Testing Issues- Pregnant Women, confidentiality, loss of insurance- Agendas/minutes for meeting, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Internet Information- Email address lists, websites for further information on subjects, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Jenkins, Heidi "The State of the State of STDs in Connecticut" Department of Public Health, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Latino Summit on HIV/AIDS- Hartford, CT- Conference materials, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Leeway- Non Profit group to provide in-patient care for people living with HIV/AIDS, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Legislative Agenda- Cuts to Medicaid, increased funds for AIDS prevention, employment of HIV/AIDS patients; phone number list, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Legislative Report- Betty Gallo and Co., 1998 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Letters of Support, Grants received, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Letters of Support to other organizations from Steve Gavron., 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Letters to the Editor (various publications), 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - A Life Campaign- "Hot" issues, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - A Life Campaign- Letters to state officials, rallying events, various issue information, campaign information, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - A Life Campaign- Letters to state officials, rallying events, various issue information, campaign information, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - A Life Campaign- Letters to state officials, rallying events, various issue information, campaign information, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - A Life Campaign- Letters to state officials, rallying events, various issue information, campaign information, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - A Life Campaign- Letters to state officials, rallying events, various issue information, campaign information, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - A Life Campaign- Letters to state officials, rallying events, various issue information, campaign information, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - A Life Campaign- Letters to state officials, rallying events, various issue information, campaign information, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - A Life Campaign- Letters to state officials, rallying events, various issue information, campaign information, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - A Life Campaign- Letters to state officials, rallying events, various issue information, campaign information, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Mandatory Testing- Background, problems, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Medicaid- Block Grant Concerns, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Medicaid- Copay changes and health care advocacy, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Medicaid- Preferred Drug Formulary list changes- Legislation, articles (from Florida) about lawsuits, speaking points, correspondence (John Bonelli & legislators), 1996; 2002 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Medicaid Managed Care- Meetings, information, correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Medicaid Personal Assistance Services- Official Reports, 1991-1995 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - "Medical Alert" Periodical- The National Association of People with AIDS (NAPWA), 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Medical marijuana- Fact sheets, informational events, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Medical marijuana- Legislation and testimonies, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Meeting locations & directions (various), undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Meriden Record Journal- Arson of proposed affordable housing project, August, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - MicroGeneSys (AIDS Vaccine)- Newspaper articles regarding termination of president, correspondence, 1994; 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Milner, Thirman- Interview notes (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Financial paperwork (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Political Issues (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Unrelated Topics (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - MSM and Risk Reduction- "Preliminary Report on the Risk Dynamics in HIV + Men Who Have Sex With Men.", 1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - National AIDS Fund- Year-End Report, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - National AIDS Treatment Information Project- Common medical issues associated with HIV (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - National Alliance of State and Territorial AIDS Directors (NASTAD)- Memos, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - National Association of People With AIDS (NAPWA)- Notes, publications, membership information, Community Report (3), action alerts, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - National Association of Social Workers- Community Organizer Network Meeting agendas/notes, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - National Minority AIDS Council- Conference Bulletin periodical, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - National Minority AIDS Council- "Technical Assistance" & "Treatment Alert" Newsletters, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Needle and Syringe Exchange Programs, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - New England AIDS Education and Training Center- Newsline periodical, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - New England Rural AIDS Institute/Rural AIDS Network- Conference, prospectus, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - New Haven Home Recovery- "News From Home" periodical, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - New Haven Mayor's Task Force on AIDS- Meeting Agenda/Minutes, 1996; 2003 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper, journal, and magazine articles regarding CAAC activity/members, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Nonprofit Organization resources- Nonprofit Resource Center information, CARF "The Nonprofit Advantage", 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Northeast Regional Pride (NERP)- Conference papers (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Office of AIDS Research- Levine Report (AIDS Research program), 1996 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Office of Health Care Access (OHCA)- Chosing Advisory Committee- Nominee Steve Gavron, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Op Ed Piece for Courant "Medicaid Cuts Deadly to People With AIDS" by Steve Gavron, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - "Organizing Strategy Chart" Photocopy from unknown book, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Pegasys Medication- Hepatitis C- Review in The New England Journal of Medicine, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - People Living with HIV (PLWH) Sourcebook Involving People Living with HIV Disease in Titles I and II of the Ryan White Care Act, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Pequot Community Foundation- Grant Application, responses, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Peters Retreat- "War group fighting" letters to the editor, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Photographs- Activist meeting- Funding for housing & War on AIDS (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Positive Action Committee- New Britain- Meeting agenda, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Positive Action Conference "A Conference for People with HIV"- Folder with conference materials, November 21, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Positive Outlook! Conference "A Day for People with HIV"- Folder (2) with conference materials., July 23, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Presidential Advisory Council on HIV/AIDS- Report, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Presidential Election- George Bush v. John Kerry- Articles, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Press Releases - "How to", n.d. (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Prison overcrowding- Prison reform legislation, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Project Inform- Newsletter, fact sheet, medication information, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Project Inform/ Project Tan (Treatment Action Network) Inform- Political Action Alerts, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Provincetown Positive periodical, 1994, 1995, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Pro Visions 1 "The New England Community Conference on HIV"- Conference materials, September, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Pro Visions 3- Conference materials, April, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Pro Visions 4- Conference materials, June, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Pro Visions 5- Conference materials, June, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Pro Visions 6- Conference materials, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Pro Visions 7- Conference materials, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Pro Visions 8- Conference materials, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Rental Assistance Program- Changes to regulations hearing, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - "Report of the Mayor's Blue Ribbon Task Force on Public Health," Hartford, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Respect Youth Project- Guide to sexual orientation, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - ROOTZ- Elder's Guide Book binder- Group for gay and bisexual men (Box 5)
  - Rowland, John Governor responses to letters, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Ryan White Care Act- Reauthorization Bill (Funding for AIDS/HIV patient's needs)- Letters, alerts & Program Review (2000), 1995; 2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Ryan White Title I- Planning Council- Greater Hartford- Meeting agendas, resources fact sheet, 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Ryan White Title I & II- Planning Council of New Haven and Fairfield Counties- Needs Assessment Survey, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Ryan White Title II- Greater Hartford Consortium, 1997; 2003 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Ryan White Title II- Regional Consortium- Work group schedule, brochures, Hartford, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Ryan White Statewide HIV Care Consortium- Meeting notice, agenda, correspondence, notes., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Ryan White Statewide HIV Care Consortium- By-laws, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Ryan White Year 6 Plan/Public Hearing, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Safe Water Drinking Act- Press releases, information, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Sexually Transmitted Diseases & Microbicides- Information, research, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Society for Non Profit Organizations- Membership information, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Solan, Mark- State Attorney - Presentation at the Willimantic Downtown Business Council's Quarterly Meeting regarding drug use and needle exhange in Willimantic, May 15, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Southeastern Connecticut Ryan White Consortium- Bylaws (New London), 1995; 2001 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Southeastern Connecticut Ryan White Title II Regional Consortium New London Training, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - State Ethics Commission Newsletter, April 1998 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Statewide HIV Care Consortium- Meetings, planning, budgets, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Statewide HIV Care Consortium- Meetings, planning, budgets, July 1, 1995 - June 30, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - "Stop Cutting the HIV/AIDS Budget!" Campaign, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - "Stop Global AIDS Now!"- Rally call email., 2001 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Surveys- Information gathered for community resource guide (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - T. B. Transmissions- Connecticut Periodical, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Testing Policies, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - The Living Center- Community center for people with AIDS- brochures, newsletter, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - "The State of Lesbian and Gay Rights in the United States" No date/author (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - The United States Conference on AIDS "Remembering the Past...Building the Future"- Conference materials, handouts, notes, 2000; 2003 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Trinity College & Steve Gavron correspondence, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Trinity Hill Healthcare Center- New HIV/AIDS designated unit, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - True Colors- Safe Schools Task Force- Meeting notes, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Tuberculosis Control & HIV Infection in Connecticut- American Lung Association publication, memos, legislation, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Unite Hartford Unido- Campaigning materials, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - United States Department of Health and Human Services- CAAC correspondence, news, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - University of Connecticut- Employment opportunities from CAAC, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Vilardi, Frank- Evening Honoring Frank Vilardi, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Viral Load Testing- Information about, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Weinstein, Beth- World AIDS Day- Presented with an award, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - William and Mary Gay and Lesbian Alumni- "Some Straight Talk About Homosexuality," n.d. (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Women Voting For Our Future- Newsletter, surveys, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - World AIDS Day- Poster, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Yale University- Center for Interdisciplinary Research on AIDS (CIRA)- Research Summary, Newsletter, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Youth & HIV/AIDS: An American Agenda- Report to the president, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 41)